http://www.htfr.com/pages/content/privacy.php

Just In
Featured VinylSee all...
INNER CITY DO YOU LOVE WHAT YOU FEEL TEN 1989UK 12" £4.99
D-KNOX STRING MAJOR E.P. SONIC MIND 2001USA 12" £5.99
THE USED VULNERABLE HOPELESS RECORDS 2012ALBUM(I) £9.99
VARIOUS ARTISTS THANK GOD IT'S FRIDAY (THE ORIGINAL MOTION PICTURE SOUNDTRACK) CASABLANCA 19783 X LP £19.99
THE BEATMASTERS FEATURING BETTY BOO HEY DJ RHYTHM KING RECORDS 1989UK 12" £4.99
SINITTA LOVE & AFFECTION (DNA REMIX) FANFARE RECORDS 1990UK 12" £5.99
THE INCREDIBLE KRAZE LET ME LOVE YOU WEST 2 RECORDINGS 1997UK(P) £5.99
JK25 LET IT ALL HANG OUT '90 MCA 1990UK 12" £5.99
CHAMPAGNE DIVINE INSPIRATION BONAFIDE 2005UK(P) £4.99
Vinyl Genres
Browse Vinyl & CD Genres See all...
Browse Artists
Browse Top Vinyl & CD Artists / Groups See all...
Browse Label
Browse Top Vinyl & CD Record Labels See all...
Browse Formats
Browse Vinyl & CD Formats See all...
Acetate 12"
Australian 12"
Austrian 12"
Belgium 12"
Canadian 12"
Double Compact Disc
Dutch 12"
Dutch Promo 12"
Four Album Pack
French 12"
French Promo 12"
German 12"
German Double 12"
German Promo 12"
Import Album
Import CD
Import Double Album
Import Double CD
Italian 12"
Italian Double 12"
Jamaican 7"
Jamaican 12"
Spanish 12"
Swedish 12"
Swiss 12"
Three Album Pack
UK 10"
UK 12"
UK 7"
UK Double 12"
UK Double Promo 12"
UK Promo 10"
UK Promo 12"
UK Test Pressing
US 7"
US Double 12"
US Double Promo 12"
US Import 12"
US Promo 12"
> Terms & Conditions
> How Do I Order?
> How Do I Pay?
> How Do I Contact HTFR?
> How Do I Sell Vinyl to HTFR?
> Returning An Item
> FAQs
Privacy Policy
How we use and protect your information
This privacy policy outlines how Hard To Find Records protect and utilise any information that you provide us.
We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is 100% protected. We may ask you to provide information for security or operational purposes when using this website. You can be assured that this information will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Hard To Find Records reserves the right to amend this policy. We recommend you check this page occasionally to ensure that you are comfortable with any changes.
Relevant Legislation
Our business, computer systems and website are all built to comply with the following national and international user privacy and data protection legislation:
UK Data Protection Act 1988 (DPA)
EU Data Protection Directive 1995 (DPD)
EU General Data Protection Regulation 2018 (GDPR)
Australian Privacy Act 1988 (APA)
If you are unsure if this website is compliant with your own countries data protection and user privacy legislation, please contact sales@htfr.com
What we collect
We may collect the following information to ensure a more pleasant and efficient experience for our customers:
Name(s), address(es) and contact information.
Site visitation tracking via Google Analytics (GA)
Preferences and interests.
Your order history.
Any other information relevant to future customer surveys and/or offers.
We do not collect or capture ANY of your financial data.
What we do with the information we gather
We request the above information in an attempt to better understand your needs and provide you with a better service. Additional uses may include:
Internal record keeping.
Improvements in our products and services.
We may send promotional emails regarding offers, website developments or other information we think you will find interesting. We use Mailjet to send our newsletter. If you are subscribed, the email address you used will be forward to them. However, your email address will not be stored in their database.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Not all email servers are secured. Please always consider email an insecure medium. Please do not include any sensitive information within an email.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file on your computer allowing web applications to respond to you as an individual. We use cookies to log website traffic and general user preferences. We also use them to maintain your basket should you wish to purchase later.
We do not use cookies to store any personal information that could be traced back to you as an individual.
By using this website, you implicitly consent to the use of cookies.
Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at www.AboutCookies.org. Please note, by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
If you feel you no longer wish Hard To Find Records to keep any information, you may opt out and close your account at any time by sending an email to sales@htfr.com
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at sales@htfr.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties. Exceptions include third party couriers, Google and Mailjet. We may also need to share your information if we are required to do so by law.
We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email sales@htfr.com
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email or write to us. We will promptly correct any personal information that is incorrect.
Data Breach Policy
In the unlikely event of a data breach, we will inform the relevant persons and authorities within 72 hours of the breach.
Data Controller
The data controller of this website is: Hard To Find Digital Ltd, a UK Private limited Company with company number 05515214
Whose registered office is:
9-11 Vittoria St, Birmingham, B1 3ND
And whose operating office is:
ABOUT US:
HTFR is a worldwide mail order store supplying the worlds best selection of Vinyl records.
CONTACT US: (Warehouse only)
HTFR, 28 Hall Street,
Birmingham, B18 6BS Tel: 08456 803 406 (10am - 5pm) sales@htfr.com
All orders subject to our terms & conditions © 2020 HTFR - all rights reserved
USEFUL LINKS:
Added to basket:
Continue shopping...
View my basket...
Added to basket:
Continue shopping...
View my wishlist...
